http://www.gisearch.com/terms/

Terms of Service Member Login
The following Terms of Service ("Terms") apply to You an Your use of the GIsearch.com. These Terms are an agreement between You and GIsearch. It is important that You understand both the benefits we provide as well as our limitations.
1. Acceptance of Terms.
If You complete the member registration process online, You will agree to these Terms by clicking the "I Accept" button. If You complete a paper member registration form (not online), You agree to these terms by signing at the bottom of the GIsearch.com registration form. These Terms may be updated from time to time, and You are bound by all such changes so You should read these Terms each time You access the GIsearch web site. If You do not click the "I Accept" button agreeing to these Terms, or initial the hard copy member registration form, You will not be permitted to use or access certain portions or services of this web site. You can review the most current version of these Terms at any time at: http://www.GIsearch.com/info/termsofservice.php. Also, when using services offered through GIsearch third party service providers, You will be subject to terms posted by our service providers. Use of their services signifies Your agreement to those additional terms.
2. Benefits of Joining.
(a) GIsearch Services. As part of our dedication to our community, we currently provide users with access to a vast collection of information about current and former U.S. Military Personnel from all over the world. We also provide various communications tools which help You stay in touch with, contact, or renew friendships with military personnel. In addition, we may provide online forums, shopping services, personalized content and branded programming through GIsearch's web site or its services, collectively the "Services". GIsearch's Services are presently provided free of charge, although some of our service providers' services and some future GIsearch Services may be subject to a charge.
Service Limitations. We will try very hard to make Your experience with GIsearch a pleasurable one. However, we cannot always foresee or anticipate technical or other difficulties. These difficulties may result in loss of data, personalization settings or other service interruptions. You agree that GIsearch's Services are provided "AS-IS". GIsearch cannot assume responsibility for the timeliness, deletion, mis-delivery or failure to store any user data, communications or personalization settings.
Service Changes and Discontinuation. GIsearch reserves the right to change or discontinue, temporarily or permanently, the Service at any time without notice. You agree that GIsearch will not be liable to You or any third party for any modification or discontinuance of the Service.
Privacy Policy. GIsearch respects Your privacy. The information You provide helps us make GIsearch more fun and useful for You. It also enables us to give You updates about our Service. We use technology and agreements to protect personally identifiable information that You provide (like Your name, age and email address). You should not receive any unauthorized email or postal mail from third parties as a result of giving information to GIsearch. Please keep in mind that whenever You voluntarily disclose personal information in GIsearch's public areas, that information can be collected and used by others. The complete terms of our Privacy Policy are part of this agreement so You should read it. http://www.GIsearch.com/info/privacy.php
Cancellation. You may cancel Your GIsearch membership at any time by clicking on the "Cancel Service" link found on Your Member Toolbox page. Please keep in mind that extended periods of inactivity may result in Your account being canceled. So, please remember to visit us regularly.
3. Mandatory Procedures and Guidelines.
For the benefit of the entire GIsearch community, and to comply with applicable laws, we have a few mandatory guidelines. We hope You will find them reasonable. Please understand, though, that any conduct that violates these procedures and guidelines is grounds for termination of Your account. For this reason, we ask that You carefully read and follow them.
Provide Accurate Information. You agree to provide true, accurate, current and complete information about Yourself as requested in GIsearch's registration form and in the military personnel registration area. (We call this collective information "Registration Data".) Accurate records help us create a better site and provide us with opportunities to identify new services or products that may interest You. Please update the Registration Data to keep it current and accurate.
Guard Your Password. You will receive a password and username upon completing the registration process. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of Your password and username. And You are fully responsible for all activities that occur using Your password or username. Please notify GIsearch immediately of any unauthorized use of Your password or username or any other breach of security.
Obey the Law. You agree not to use the Service for illegal purposes or for the transmission of material that is unlawful, harassing, libelous (untrue and damaging to others), violative and/or invasive of another's privacy, abusive, threatening, or obscene, or that infringes the copyrights (rights of an owner of written material) or other intellectual property of others.
Use E-mail Wisely. GIsearch may provide its members with access to a free email account. In return for this free access, You agree not to use the Service to broadcast "junk mail", "spam", "chain letters", or unsolicited mass distribution of files or images. To ensure that our email Service is not abused, GIsearch may establish general practices and limits concerning use of the email Service. These may include but are not necessarily limited to a maximum number of days that e-mail messages will be retained by the Service, a maximum number of email messages that may be sent from or received by an account on the Service, a maximum size of any email message that may be sent from or received by an account on the Service, a maximum amount of disk space that will be allotted for Your email, and a maximum time period and number of times You may have access to the Service in a given time frame.
Restrictions on Resale. GIsearch attempts to provide some of the very best content available on the web. In order to provide this content to You, however, we must restrict publication as well as redistribution of text, photos, graphics, audio and/or video materials in any form or medium. Neither content created by GIsearch nor content licensed to GIsearch by its service providers (or any portion of such content) may be stored in a computer, except for personal and noncommercial use.
4. Rights You Grant to GIsearch.
Distributing Content You Produce. Subject to GIsearch's Privacy Policy, which is described above and available at Privacy Policy Link, You, are licensing to GIsearch any "Content" You provide through or to GIsearch and the Service. GIsearch may modify, display, distribute and create new material using such Content on GIsearch's affiliated networks for the promotion and marketing of our services. By submitting Content, You automatically agree, or promise that the owner of such Content has expressly agreed that, without any particular time limit, and without the payment of any fees, GIsearch and anyone GIsearch permits may reproduce, display, distribute and create new works of authorship based on and including the Content.
GIsearch Advertising. GIsearch relies on advertisers to help fund the Services that we offer to our members. In order to continue our free service, unless You are a Paid member, You agree that GIsearch may display advertisements and promotions of all kinds in and with the Services. If you are a paid member you will not see any ads on the site unless you opt in to them.
Account Access. In order to ensure that GIsearch is able to provide high quality Services that are responsive to members' needs, You agree that GIsearch employees may have access to Your account and records as reasonably needed to investigate complaints.
5. Additional Legal Matters.
DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES. YOU EXPRESSLY UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT: YOUR USE OF THE SERVICE, INCLUDING ANY OTHER WEB SITES LINKED TO THE GISEARCH SITE, IS AT YOUR SOLE EXCLUSIVE RISK. THE SERVICE IS PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" AND "AS AVAILABLE" BASIS. GISEARCH EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT. GISEARCH MAKES NO WARRANTY THAT (I) THE SERVICE WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS, (ii) THE SERVICE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED, TIMELY, SECURE, OR ERROR-FREE, (iii) THE RESULTS THAT MAY BE OBTAINED FROM THE USE OF THE SERVICE WILL BE ACCURATE OR RELIABLE, (iv) THE QUALITY OF ANY PRODUCTS, SERVICES, INFORMATION, OR OTHER MATERIAL PURCHASED OR OBTAINED BY YOU THROUGH THE SERVICE WILL MEET YOUR EXPECTATIONS, AND (v) ANY ERRORS IN THE SOFTWARE WILL BE CORRECTED. ANY MATERIAL DOWNLOADED OR OTHERWISE OBTAINED THROUGH THE USE OF THE SERVICE IS DONE AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION AND RISK AND YOU ARE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGE TO YOUR COMPUTER SYSTEM OR LOSS OF DATA THAT RESULTS FROM THE DOWNLOAD OF ANY SUCH MATERIAL. NO ADVICE OR INFORMATION, WHETHER ORAL OR WRITTEN, OBTAINED BY YOU FROM GISEARCH OR THROUGH OR FROM THE SERVICE WILL CREATE ANY WARRANTY NOT EXPRESSLY STATED IN THESE TERMS. Some jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion of certain warranties or the limitation or exclusion of liability for incidental or consequential damages. Accordingly, some of the above GISEARCH limitations may not apply to You. TO THE EXTENT THAT ANY PART OF THIS SECTION IS NOT CONSISTENT WITH ANY OTHER PART OF THESE TERMS, THEN THIS SECTION WILL CONTROL.
No Endorsement of Member Content. You acknowledge and agree that GIsearch does not endorse or control the content of any member and is not responsible or liable for any content, even though it could be unlawful, harassing, libelous, violative and/or invasive of another's privacy, abusive, threatening, harmful, vulgar, obscene, or otherwise objectionable, or that it infringes or may infringe the intellectual property or other rights of another. You acknowledge that GIsearch does not pre-screen content, but that GIsearch and its designees will have the right (but not the obligation) in their sole discretion to refuse, edit, move or remove any content that is publicly available via the Service.
LIMITATION OF LIABILITY. YOU AGREE THAT GISEARCH WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY HARMS, WHICH LAWYERS AND COURTS OFTEN CALL DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL OR EXEMPLARY DAMAGES, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF PROFITS, GOODWILL, USE, DATA OR OTHER INTANGIBLE LOSSES, EVEN IF GISEARCH HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES, RESULTING FROM: (I) THE USE OR THE INABILITY TO USE THE SERVICE; (ii) THE COST OF GETTING SUBSTITUTE GOODS AND SERVICES RESULTING FROM ANY PRODUCTS, DATA, INFORMATION OR SERVICES PURCHASED OR OBTAINED OR MESSAGES RECEIVED OR TRANSACTIONS ENTERED INTO THROUGH OR FROM THE SERVICE; (iii) UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO OR ALTERATION OF YOUR TRANSMISSIONS OR DATA; (iv) STATEMENTS OR CONDUCT OF ANYONE ON THE SERVICE; (v) TRANSACTIONS OR CONTENT IN CONNECTION WITH ANY WEB SITES LINKED TO THE GISEARCH SITE; OR (vi) ANY OTHER MATTER RELATING TO THE SERVICE.
Indemnification. You agree to protect and fully compensate GIsearch and its affiliates, and service providers from any and all third party claims, liability, damages, expenses and costs (including, but not limited to, reasonable attorneys fees) caused by or arising from Your use of the Services, Your violation of the Terms of Service or Your infringement, or infringement by any other user of Your account, of any intellectual property or other right of anyone.
Changes in Writing. This agreement cannot be changed or any of GIsearch's rights waived unless GIsearch agrees in writing or You agree by either clicking the "I Accept" button, following any changes proposed by GIsearch or by another reasonable method requested by GIsearch. You may assign this agreement only with GIsearch's written approval. Any notices related to the agreement described in these Terms need to GIsearch at its addresses below, or any new address that is given in such a notice. The laws of the State of South Carolina apply to this agreement. These Terms are the entire understanding between You and GIsearch about the Services.
Members
01  02  03  04  05  06  07  08  09  10  11  12  13  14  15  16  17  1819  20  21  22  23  24  25  26  27  28  29  30  31  32  33  34  35  3637  38  39  40  41  42  43  44  45  46  47  48  49  50  51  52  53
Quick Links
About Us
Contact Us
Privacy Policy
Terms of Service
Recent Searches
About GI Search
GI Search is a free military search and military social network helping search, locate,
and stay in touch with the military friends and loved ones in the Army, Air Force,
Navy, Marine Corps and Coast Guard. Search for anyone who was or is in the military or browse through the archive photos of bases, aircraft, naval ships.
GI Search partners with recreational classifieds featuring
and .
Copyright © 1999-2020		This GI Search page loaded in
0.0002751350402832		seconds
